Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Oster, born unable to harness mana,
was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad
also possessed powers from the devils of the Underworld
and used them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself
and from the support of his friends,
Oster continues to fight for the safety of this world.
I don't care how fast or determined you are,
it won't help you now.
Skin magic, skin for it!
True lightning magic, Kanados!
Svenkin, a dark disciple who attacked the Heart Kingdom
on Earthanica's command, was soundly defeated by luck.
Meanwhile, the Black Bull's hideout was ambushed by Dante,
one of the Dark Triad.
Don't do it!
Oh no!
With an unknown spell, Grey rescued Ghosh from the brink of death.
Grey...
She sealed the wound.
I didn't know her transformation magic could do that.
What is this spell?
Asta was enraged by his friend's suffering, and his devil's power went berserk.
But it wasn't enough to stop Dante.
Magnificent!
Yet another arcane stage fighter.
Seeing Vanessa and Grey's potential, Dante tried to take them.
Then, Yami returned to the hideout.
Hey!
That's my squad.
So keep your mitts off of them.
But the captain had been Dante's target all along.
He believed Yami was the key to connecting this world with the underworld.
If they're arcane stage, then that's the first I've heard about it.
And they're not here to serve me.
I just brought them on because I liked them.
Monozone.
Condense.
But the captain had been Dante's target all along.
He believed Yami was the key to connecting this world with the underworld.
If they're arcane stage, then that's the first I've heard about it.
And they're not here to serve me. I just brought them on because I liked them.
Monozone, condense.
Dark Club to E.I. Slash.
They're not going anywhere.
Not with you, you damn freak.
Get it on, get it on,始めよう.
難航不落のリアリティー。
立ち止まる時間はないさ。
Hold on, hold on.
Yeah!
Now this time, fight for liberty.
真実性、飲み込み常識を増え。
逆境の先にある朝。
Oh yeah!
幻想に埋もれた人生の夢。
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えてもかすぐして。
Feel it! We can't face!
Let's go!
Oh! Believe in myself!
衝動的に突き進め。
Don't be afraid!
誰よりも高く飛べ。
Take it to the sky!
想像を超えた世界をこの手に。
The Grand Ole!
想像せよ。
偽りどない一面の道。
Yes! It's a Grand Ole!
Hey yeah!
Believe in myself!
Believe in yourself!
The Thunder!
Kill. I'll kill them. Kill them all. They must be. Kill. Kill.
Hold on. Killing?
Kill them all.
What the heck just happened? My body won't move at all. Wait, what about Ghosh? I can still sense his key. Good. He's alive. That jerk from space.
Using my E.I. blade, if I cast mana zone with condensed mana, then it'll never miss.
I'm surprised. I never thought anyone would make me use this magic.
This is completely different from the techniques he was using before. What's going on?
All this envy and rage and hatred. I can't get enough of it. Color me impressed, Yamisuke Hiro.
I was bored with absolutely everything.
There was nothing in this world that could slake this extreme malice.
Yummy, my friend. Believe me. This is only the beginning of what's in store. You're going to open up a brand new world for me soon.
Stop it, man. You're creeping me out. And that goatee looks awful.
You said something about me being the key to the underworld, but I got no idea what you're talking about. Pretty sure I'm not that special, pal.
Don't flatter yourself. The key to the underworld isn't you, per se. It's a magical channel known as the Tree of Klyphoth.
To bring that channel into being, we need dark magic and world tree magic, both at the arcane stage.
Which means that the crucial players here are you and William Vonchens.
So this guy knows about William's magic.
All right, let's say we do connect this world to the underworld. Then what happens?
Then this realm will become infested with devils.
And once they've taken over, every possible kind of malice will descend upon this land.
And that's sure to be awfully entertaining, right, Yami Tsukihiro?
That's it. No more chit-chat. I'm taking you down here and now.
These jerks are burning the forest, which means they're destroying the food, and there's no way I'm gonna let that happen!
Oh, lovely flames. Engulf me and my gorgeous hair in your world.
No! The palm-broom forest! We're done for!
They took down a spirit guardian!
If Ser Potrov hadn't shielded us, we would all be dead!
Consider yourselves lucky. It's true that you're about to die, but at least the immaculate beauty of Dark Disciple Halbit Shavor is the last thing you'll see.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh?
Mm-hmm. It seems an unsightly fatty has arrived.
Ser Potrov! Charmy's here!
Charmy?
Hey, it's Charmy!
Well, how about that? Did you sneak away from your training again?
Do you want to take a snack break?
I can tell how incredibly talented you are. Let's do our best!
You won't get away with this.
That's our magical sheep! Save us, Charmy!
Huh. Looks like your magic is as soft as you.
Our spells are passing right through each other. Perhaps this is what they mean when they say affinity.
But there's one major difference here.
My magic is able to protect me from incoming attacks.
But yours doesn't shield you at all, so you're wide open.
Thanks to the devil's power, my hair isn't just devastatingly beautiful. It's also impossibly strong.
Charmy!
That roly-poly little body of yours has no chance of wiggling away from me. Why bother with food?
Eating is a foolish waste of time. I've found all you really need for maximum beauty and strength is the proper nutrition.
Anyway, your fatness is an eyesore.
So I will embrace you with my beauty as you die.
Hey.
Didn't I tell you when I got here?
I won't let you get away with this.
Hey.
Didn't I tell you when I got here?
I won't let you get away with this.
What is that?
She doesn't even have devil powers.
How is she doing this?
Food magic.
Glutton's banquet.
Seems like we've got a slippery opponent on our hands.
Well then.
I'll just cook her.
What?
What's happening?
The mana method is my kitchen.
And when I use it to cook something...
Any dish becomes delicious.
And my wolf is sure to scarf it down.
Ah!
Charmy is terrifying.
I can't believe she was capable of this much destruction.
How dare you do such a thing to someone so gorgeous!
This looks pretty tasty.
Here we go.
Delvin!
Ah!
This is what you get from disrespected!
the only way to get true beauty and strength is from a balanced diet thank you for saving us
you ate that witch for dinner
they took down sir floga the fire spirit guardian even he couldn't beat these guys
i don't think i've ever seen a technique like that before how would you even dodge it that young
man from the clover kingdom doesn't stand a chance
where are you
well he's resilient that strike didn't even pierce his body
but how long can he last his mana is dwindling away by the second wherever you run pathetic
little neophyte you'll never escape being riddled with holes by dark disciple sivwar snile
i'm using an eye magic spell called katoblipus's evil eye my eyes are everywhere not only can they
track you but they gauge your mana and stamina and by watching your eye line and muscle movement
i can predict what you'll do next once i've locked onto my target i'll fire using the
shells that i make from condensed mana
and these things never miss
damn it
floga's down
i think you'll get better results if you try to focus on your strengths
my strengths like what you're the kind of person who has the strength to endure anything
i mean you're you right
i just have to sharpen my senses
there you are
flame magic
profound spiral flame
did you really think that i wouldn't be able to dodge that you fool
it doesn't matter what clever tricks the heart kingdom taught you it's no use
it took him a little longer to throw something at me this time
that's because he had to take a second to evade my attack
feel free to keep moving in closer all you want
i'll just keep creating distance
that's what i thought
we're both moving but we're not any farther apart
he's getting as far away from me as possible but staying in range to fight
no one's ever been able to injure me in a battle
in fact i've never even felt any pain
so a mere simpleton like you would be foolish to believe he could land a single hit against me
don't give up
i have to endure
until i bring him down
you don't know when to quit do you
just roll over and die
it's true
i may not have as much talent as my older brother and sister
but
with them to look up to
i've held strong and let my inner flame keep blazing
you realize that endurance isn't enough to win don't you
time to finish this
hold on
where is he
what
where did that enormous array come from
when did he have a chance to
i endured you so that i could take my time creating it
and i did the whole thing while you were so focused on keeping your eyes on me
no i have to get out of this array
true flame magic
crimson eruption
that's the biggest array i've ever seen in my life
it's gonna burn me to a crisp
i never learned how to deal with pain
i've gone my entire life without enduring so much as a scratch
how dare you do this to me
thanks for making so much noise
now i know exactly where you are
you don't get to whine about the pain you're in after all the suffering you've caused
no
stop
if you're not tough enough to handle getting burned
you're finished here dark disciple
amazing
thank you sir gaja
i've gotta hand it to you gaja
you really are an incredible fighter
even among the guardians
i didn't think i would make it in time
now i need to get everyone to safety
and return to queen lorapetchka
they defeated all the dark disciples
excellent fighting everyone
yeah whatever i guess they did all right
that was amazing i'm so happy they're all okay
i'm grateful they could defend the places where my water couldn't reach
no matter how strong their foes are
the clover kingdom magic knights evolve their skills to match
even mid combat
oh my i set the mana of some delicious ladies in here
we knew you'd show up eventually
that's right we're prepared
plant magic magic cannon flower
serves you right for being creepy
that was a wonderful technique mimosa
it wouldn't have been possible without all that mana you sent me
this mana it's so sinister
i haven't seen you in so long
so i came to play
happy to see me little lorapetchka
beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful
ゆーわけ前の空静かにそっとほら新たな日々が始まる
meio明け前の空 静かにそっと
ほら新たな日々が始まる
胸に伸ばり込んだままの想いを解き放って
その翼を広げて..
more time
I'm going to fly now
I'm going to the sea of the sea
I'm going to be closer to anyone
I'm going to fly
Beautiful
I'm going to see you
So I'm always beside you
And never let go
Boku no kou no te wo
Anasanaide tooko matemo
Tzitekite hooshii
The world is so beautiful
Clovercust
The strength to endure
I bet you're getting close to the end of your rope, Charmy
The heck are you talking about? This is easy breezy
You don't need to push yourself either, Leo
Don't be ridiculous, Floga showed me how to maximize my endurance
And I'm going to use those lessons to defeat you
Wait and see
Go ahead and hop on out, Charmy
And nobody's going to judge you, I promise
No way, you're the one who needs to get out
You look like a pig and green popsicle
Leo, didn't you say you're not good with the cold?
I've got the strength to endure
They're so lively
Banika, I won't let you have your way any longer
Because now I have friends I can depend on to help
Black Clover, page 165
Water Crusade
Today's the day we end this fight